vivalogo.com 2010-11-13

# Logo Design by Vivalogo - Privacy Policy

## Vivalogo™ Privacy Policy

Logo Design Privacy Policy

Vivalogo is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable Web experience possible. While you can use many features of Vivalogo anonymously, you are required to provide personal information to gain access to some of our premium content and services. 

**How we collect and use personal information**

When you complete our order form we collect information about you and your business to aid in the design of your logo or other graphic design services. The information we collect from you is never shared with any other company and is treated as confidential. 

We also work tirelessly to make sure that we use any information you provide us only in ways you have approved. 

**How we use "cookies"**

We only use "cookies" in our Client Area to provide secure logging in. As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site (except ofcourse the Client Area). 

**What we provide to third parties**

It is important to note that VivaLogo does not process orders directly. We use reputable ecommerce company - Share-It, Inc. to do this on our behalf using the very latest in secure transmission technologies. It is very important for Share-It to keep accurate purchase records. Share-It will pass on the following details when you purchase one of our packages to us - name, company name, e-mail address, and other relevant contact details. This data is used only to identify you in order to give you the full benefits of your purchase. Please note that we do not receive a copy of your actual payment details (such as Credit card numbers or Wire transfer details). We do not make any of this information available to any third parties. To learn more about our ecommerce vendor`s privacy & security policies, payment,...click here  

Obtaining your consent

By using our Web site, you give Vivalogo permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. 

If you are under the age of 18, you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law. 

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

VivaLogo is not responsible for the privacy policies of Web sites to which this site may link.

#### Don't take our word for it

We are very pleased with our new logo, the design process was very enjoyable and enabled us select a new logo very quickly and painlessly! ...  
_John King, Huntsman Estate Agents_

#### 100% Satisfaction Guarantee

Vivalogo wants satisfied customers. No matter what. That`s why we guarantee your full satisfaction, or your [money back](http://www.vivalogo.com/logo-design-pages/viva-logo-guarantee.htm).
